<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Shuggeffect]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Shuggeffect]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:05:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EVERYTHING IS ART]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>EVERYTHING IS ART</h1><p>You are an artist… because everything is art. Loving others is “art” Good parenting is “art” Good teaching is “art” Learning is “art” Healthy living is “art” You get it….everything is “art.” My daughter has an art class one day a week at her school. She loves it. They do a great job helping her draw and paint scenarios she has experienced. Maybe it’s a trip we’ve made or her just playing with her cousins outside. But, then at home there are the times I’ll see her grab her crayons and a sheet of paper and just draw shapes, glue pieces of paper and add glitter. Then she’ll ask me, “Daddy is this art?” I always respond, “Everything is art.” Art is the expression or application of human creative skill and imagination. (apple dictionary) Do you see yourself as an artist? You should. You have lots of creative “one of a kind” bones in your body. You’re the only one of you. One of the most important parts of art is that it encourages a reaction. Most of us look to encourage a positive reaction. A reaction that attracts. A reaction that motivates. A reaction that supports our personal values. When my daughter asks me if what she created is art, what impresses me the most is that she doesn’t ask me if it is “good” art. She doesn’t have to ask. Based on my reaction, she knows it is something that brings a smile to my face, so she’ll try it again. When you see yourself as an artist you won’t rest on successes because you’ll never stop creating and you aren’t destroyed by your failures because all you did was get that one out of the way. Take the time to glean knowledge and experience from those who went before you, ask why, and learn. Then make art. You are making art whether you know it or not. So, if you’re going to sit down in front of a canvas, might as well make it an original. </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5eb33184-7fbc-4671-8176-d65839a1e06d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/everything-is-art/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">776933ec-e0e2-49a4-8e52-bcf807386d19</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:05:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[1+1+1 = 99]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>1+1+1 = 99</h1><p>Last night, on my way home from work, I called my wife and I could tell she was pretty stressed out. The kids had gotten on her last nerve. My son pooped his pants three times, he peed on the floor, and he and his sister wouldn’t stop bickering. 3 things throughout the day had brought some stress, but just 3? From the time we were little, we were taught that 1+1+1 = 3. But from the above example we see, with the right circumstances, 1+1+1 can equal WAY more than 3. It can feel like 1+1+1 = 99. So, when the right things get added in the right way at the right time, addition and subtraction rules get thrown out the window. Synergy – the interaction of elements that when combined produce a total effect that is greater than the sum of the individual elements, contributions, etc.; synergism. Most kids are masters of synergy. They can make you feel like there are several hundred of them, when in fact, there are just 2 or 3. But what about positive synergy? When, as a group, you can recognize and cultivate the different strengths that everyone individually can bring to the table, the result can be much more than just adding up the number of people. Don’t limit yourself to think that adding someone to your 5 person team will equal 6. It could equal much more than that, but it has to be the right person, in the right way, and at the right time. If you’re the one adding to a team, don’t demand synergy…provide the best opportunity for it. If you’re the team being added to, envision the opportunity each addition will bring. The exponential growth is up to you…whoever you are. </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8924f3b3-ac15-4be7-96ea-013e31cccf7d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/111-99/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2f0f9c6c-a036-4981-8586-bc4b0a97dd8f</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:05:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I’ll poop on the potty on Friday. ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>I’ll poop on the potty on Friday. </h1><p>So, my wife and I are working on potty training our three year old little boy… He just won’t get excited about going poop on the toilet. When he poops in his diaper, I ask him when he is going to start pooping on the potty? Every time, he responds, “I’ll poop on the potty on Friday.” It doesn’t matter what day it is…he always tells me he’ll do it on Friday. I’m not sure why he picks Fridays and I’m not sure he even knows why he picks Fridays. What he does know, is that he will handle that later. He’ll put it on the schedule. He’ll give it a date and plan, so I’ll feel better about letting it wait. I’m sure you can guess what happens when Friday rolls around. You got it, he tells me he’ll do it next Friday. Again, he’ll schedule it and try to make me feel good that he is planning for it. Obviously, I know it can’t continue this way, but his example really made me think if I figuratively schedule myself to poop on Fridays? Do I consistently push things that need to get done? Do I schedule them, reschedule them, and then reschedule them without any real intent to get it done, until it becomes absolutely urgent? I recognized that my 3 year old and I had a lot in common. We, both in our own way, will poop on Fridays. My advice to him would be, “You’ll feel so good when you go on the potty. You’ll feel good that you did something you were scared to do yesterday. Most of all, you’ll feel so good and free that you don’t have to walk around everyday with poop in your pants.” Could I take my own advice? Absolutely! When I put off things until tomorrow or procrastinate I need to see myself as walking around with a “stinky load” in my pants. Don’t wait until Friday to get done what you need to. Realistically, schedule yourself. Set out to accomplish you’re plan. Know that your day will not go as planned, so plan for that. Don’t take short cuts like buying a great smelling air freshener to mask the “stinky load” you’re carrying around. Take advantage of the freedom and exuberance you’ll feel when you can release yourself of those tasks that have been binding you up…and don’t wait until Friday. This freedom can be and should be felt daily.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7017afe8-b42d-4259-b593-fe9a178c162e.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/ill-poop-on-the-potty-on-friday/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">529b1772-a925-449e-9129-14e08fdbff23</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Read Books...It Makes You More Smarter]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a6771956-0e83-4d10-8c10-6e537ced76a4.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://www.leeprint.com/blog/2015/11/25/read-books-it-makes-you-more-smarter/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8a814c0a-7555-4ea2-8021-fc6916376d13</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:04:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BE DIFFERENT]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>BE DIFFERENT</h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a0afabfccdee3f7be19e831a7a3255bad90faab1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/be-different/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4cee576a-5f19-43f5-aa60-dbbc105995b4</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WHAT IF…]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>WHAT IF…</h1><p>What would you say to someone if they said they just wanted to eat candy and lose weight? What if someone told you they wanted to get somewhere fast, but they wanted to crawl there? What about if someone told you that they wanted to be a better person, but didn’t want to learn anything? Of course, we would say this person is crazy. You can’t get what you want by doing the opposite of what you’re trying to accomplish. Not really a shocker, right? Well, what if someone told you that they wanted more clients, but they didn’t want to treat the ones they have like gold? What if a friend told you he wanted committed employees, but he didn’t want to take the time to make them feel like they mattered? What if another friend told you she wanted to start a company that inspired people, but only if the inspiration resulted in a sale? While the second set of examples sound just as crazy, many businesses operate daily with the assumption that they’ll get the desired results by doing the opposite of what really works. If you want more clients you must, must, must treat the ones you currently have like gold. If you want committed employees you must listen to them and treat them like people and not things. An inspiring company attracts, period. Don’t hinge inspiration on what you’ll get back…just give it. If you want to grow in a way that really lasts, you must consider the whole package. If you skip something or slack off in one area the whole operation suffers. Instead of saying “what if” as a way of seeing how little you can get away with, start saying “what if” I gave a little more or “what if” I went out of my way. It will certainly bring the results you desire.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/1d0350a33e82d6cdf8554b0c6ab75d9c3f60e303.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/what-if/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">29b94477-49ab-47c4-a6ab-76656ada0408</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 17:59:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[THE HISTORY OF LEE PRINTING]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>THE HISTORY OF LEE PRINTING</h1><p>Bruce Lee</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f47e6adb86aa427deff160cc3c1042c38635c17b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/the-history-of-lee-printing/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">89ca3e0c-f74c-453e-83bb-3d5354111516</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 10:53:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[THE SECRET TO BEING #1 ON ANY GOOGLE SEARCH]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>THE SECRET TO BEING #1 ON ANY GOOGLE SEARCH</h1><p>Last week I was able to go to my first Daddy Daughter dance, and I had an absolute blast! It was a memory that I will always hold near and dear to my heart. When we arrived I was relieved of a fear that my little girl would be nervously attached to my leg. I was happy to see her dancing right in the middle of all the action. It was a mosh pit of little girls dancing to all their favorite songs. I was proud to see my little Ava had invested herself with enough of the girls that it carried over into the evening. Over the school year, she must have become invested with her friends through playing together, helping each other, and in some way giving and receiving value to each other. Then, when the big night came, it was organic (a natural occurrence) that she would be where the action was. I couldn’t have paid to have this happen if I wanted to. Ava and her friends could teach us a few things about making it up the Google ladder. Yes, a bunch of six-year-olds could teach us a thing or two. Maybe, just maybe, it isn’t about paying for someone to get your website to the top, or creating some hidden code that makes Google think you are more relevant and valuable than you really are. Maybe it is actually about being valuable? If you take the time to invest in your customers, allow them to provide honest feedback, provide them with valuable resources, and make it difficult for them not to talk positively about you with their friends, Google will have no choice but to bring you up the list. Regardless of their “new” algorithm. Sound like too much work? Sounds like it would take too long? If you’re looking for true, lasting friends/customers that will jump in the mosh pit with you, then there is no alternative. Bring value with what you do and you won’t have to rely on tactics and tricks. You’ll organically grow relationships that will last much longer than any paid click or search. Sometimes, it literally pays to think like a six- year-old.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a3f563f459f850d26167dd18123f581ee5ba8b97.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/the-secret-to-being-1-on-any-google-search/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c46eb022-50db-4f5d-bd11-804d437f4f48</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 10:53:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>