<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Shuggeffect]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Shuggeffect]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:13:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ARE YOU A WINNER?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/85b7f8b0-9673-4e8e-a0d8-0f254a03cd7a.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/are-you-a-winner/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">085ad0fa-324c-44fa-9e3a-3c9137bc42e4</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:13:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[THE SECRET TO BEING #1 ON ANY GOOGLE SEARCH]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>THE SECRET TO BEING #1 ON ANY GOOGLE SEARCH</h1><p>Last week I was able to go to my first Daddy Daughter dance, and I had an absolute blast! It was a memory that I will always hold near and dear to my heart. When we arrived I was relieved of a fear that my little girl would be nervously attached to my leg. I was happy to see her dancing right in the middle of all the action. It was a mosh pit of little girls dancing to all their favorite songs. I was proud to see my little Ava had invested herself with enough of the girls that it carried over into the evening. Over the school year, she must have become invested with her friends through playing together, helping each other, and in some way giving and receiving value to each other. Then, when the big night came, it was organic (a natural occurrence) that she would be where the action was. I couldn’t have paid to have this happen if I wanted to. Ava and her friends could teach us a few things about making it up the Google ladder. Yes, a bunch of six-year-olds could teach us a thing or two. Maybe, just maybe, it isn’t about paying for someone to get your website to the top, or creating some hidden code that makes Google think you are more relevant and valuable than you really are. Maybe it is actually about being valuable? If you take the time to invest in your customers, allow them to provide honest feedback, provide them with valuable resources, and make it difficult for them not to talk positively about you with their friends, Google will have no choice but to bring you up the list. Regardless of their “new” algorithm. Sound like too much work? Sounds like it would take too long? If you’re looking for true, lasting friends/customers that will jump in the mosh pit with you, then there is no alternative. Bring value with what you do and you won’t have to rely on tactics and tricks. You’ll organically grow relationships that will last much longer than any paid click or search. Sometimes, it literally pays to think like a six- year-old.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f852b307c16a4739336228919a8819afb8436303.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/the-secret-to-being-1-on-any-google-search/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a0ef1f27-70f5-416f-9fa4-2de8aa0e3504</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:13:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Question?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Question?</h1><p>There is a question that is so simple it can be asked in one word. Most of the time, when  asked this question, we feel bothered to even try to answer it…but when WE ask it, we will search high and low for the answer. Many times, it is the most important question ever asked.

The question is…

Why?

Don’t ever be afraid to ask it and don’t be intimidated by being asked it.  The question,  “Why?” is important because it forces you, me, her, him, everyone to search and explore.

Why do we do it that way?

Why can’t we try something new?

Why is this happening?

Why isn’t that working?

Why do you feel that way?

Why do I feel this way?

The most amazing part about the question “Why?” is that the answer is not important.  When exploring the “why” of something don’t get too hung up on the answer, but see how far the successes and failures along the way bring you.  Embrace both, and maybe, just maybe, you’ll start asking yourself, “Why not?”

</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c11835fa-ab5b-4228-88b1-d52e68bd509f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/question/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6d6e1b2e-6d68-4b93-a17b-156aa43cabad</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:12:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MAKE YOUR DESIGN FIT LIKE A SUIT.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>MAKE YOUR DESIGN FIT LIKE A SUIT.</h1><p>We are surrounded every day by pleasing design. It is a part of us whether we think we enjoy it, notice it, and appreciate it or not. Billboards, magazines and commercials all try to appeal to the audience through targeted design. When shopping for clothing, we are essentially designing the way we look with color, texture, smell, and even frames. When purchasing a men’s suit, the arm length of the suit jacket should expose about ½ inch of the dress shirt sleeve, along with ½ inch of the shirt collar above the jacket collar. Why? Just to keep tailors in business? Not at all. The ½ inch of exposed shirt frames the jacket, just as a frame does with a work of art on the wall. This element is often over-looked because we are unaware or think that the extra $50-$100 in tailoring is not worth it. I guess if you’re not selling suits, and your suit sleeves are too long, it’s not the end of the world. You should know though, your suit will never look as appealing as the suit on the mannequin. So, let’s say you are trying to sell your services and you want to start marketing your business. The first option, for most, is to open MS Word or Publisher and start designing a logo. Then, find the cheapest website provider along with some free business cards. Remember, you’re trying to tell the world they should purchase from you because you’re different and BETTER than anyone else (if you’re not, don’t even bother). Imagine going to buy a suit and the gentleman helping you does not have his suit properly tailored. Maybe, you don’t know all the ins and outs of how a suit should fit, but you can definitely tell the suit on the salesman does not look like the one on the mannequin. Or…imagine, you have a contractor come to your house to give you an estimate and you inquire about his tidiness…if he’ll clean up after himself every day. You look at his vehicle and it looks like his whole office is in the truck and it hasn’t been washed in a year. No matter what the contractor tells you, there is a reluctance to believe he’ll clean up if he can’t take care of his own stuff. The “design” of a business tells more about it than any words. So, when we want to show the world who we are, it might be a good idea to get someone involved who knows the basic elements of design. There are a lot of freelance artists that are chomping at the bit to get some design work into their portfolio. Their work is very affordable. Many would be surprised at how affordable it is to get a logo/corporate identity produced. The look can be very clean and simple, but designed to be pleasing to look at. Just like it is worth the extra $50 to get that suit fitting just right, or the $10 car wash, we should put in that little extra and make design a top priority or else we are wasting our time.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/93e726b88ef6fec2c25892b7b2433ed4db0627e3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/make-your-design-fit-like-a-suit/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7df1676d-4be6-4e61-9059-c784cbcdf5db</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:12:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BORING? IT’S ALL YOUR FAULT!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>BORING? IT’S ALL YOUR FAULT!</h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/edef3ffe98cb6174183078593fd1efce218878b6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/boring-its-all-your-fault/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c7e49144-96c2-4dc2-a8bd-33030a5d3ea9</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:12:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IT’S SIMPLE…I’M HAPPY, I HAVE A HOT DOG]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>IT’S SIMPLE…I’M HAPPY, I HAVE A HOT DOG</h1><p>“I’m happy, I have a hot dog.” That was the statement made by a two-year-old. It was actually the daughter of our artist here at Lee. Kris told me what struck him was the simplicity of her happiness. He said it put life in to perspective for him. Really? Isn’t it just a cute thing said by a little toddler? I think it is way more than that. I think we can learn something from little Alessia. Basically, she told her parents simple is better. Happiness to her was not complex. She basically said, I have what I like, therefore I am happy. Her happiness was not based on expectation of the future or even what happened five minutes ago. It was simple, and her simplicity made her parents reflect. When trying to communicate a message, whether it is a marketing ad, sales brochure, or even the mission or purpose of your company…KEEP IT SIMPLE! Instead of saying, “We strive to communicate in a way that is above and beyond our customer’s expectations…” How about, “We talk so you can understand”? Simple things are remembered. Simple things provoke thought. Simple things can be re-communicated. Simple things just make sense. Don’t over-complicate things because nobody will remember a word of it…remember, “I’m happy, I have a hot dog.” </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ddde7e56-05a9-47bd-96c7-44d7a21e265b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.leeprint.com/blog/2015/10/28/its-simple-im-happy-i-have-a-hot-dog/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3282f579-a375-48ec-aba6-17da3cdff7f9</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:11:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CHANGE IS GOOD…… ALL THE TIME!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>CHANGE IS GOOD…… ALL THE TIME!</h1><p>Change is the price of progress… I got this phrase from a book I just finished. I absolutely love this phrase and I think it is entirely true. I’m the kind of person that will move the living room furniture around just because it has been the same way for too long. Not sure if that’s a good quality or a problem. Anyway, change is exciting to me. It keeps me guessing and on my toes. Change keeps me from getting complacent. It also keeps me thinking about what the next move should be. Change is good…ALL THE TIME!!!!! Allow me to explain, I was involved in a youth group and during the meetings, there was always a table located on the left side of the building where the people in charge sat. The table was on the left side of the room for as long as I can remember. We did it that way because….well um…I guess…because that’s just the way we always did it. One evening, I happened to be in charge of the meeting and I made a suggestion to my superiors that at our next meeting I was going to set the table up on the other side of the room. The response I got was along the lines of…if the change did not have a specific reason then do not do it. I could tell that the change was not exciting to the few I presented it to. So, I could not move the table. Looking back, could I have presented it better? Sure. Regardless, I could still think of about 3 billion reasons why the change would have been positive. Presentation aside, being put outside of your comfort zone is way more than just a positive. Sometimes, it can be life changing. Moving the table was not going to be life changing, but it told everyone else that we thought about the meeting, we planned, and it could have actually kept everyone guessing what would happen next. If they move the table to the other side what else could happen…I guess anything…how exciting! When I say change, I’m suggesting that we should always adapt the way we do things. The way we do all things, even a fundamental foundation like love. How can you change that? You really can’t, but you can change the way you show it and share it. When things are going good we should be thinking of the next thing to make progress. If you are not changing, then you are not progressing. So, if you’re afraid of change, then think of how scary NO PROGRESS sounds and make change your best buddy. Change is a friend when treated like one. Help it along, be gentle, handle with care, and always remember to include it in your day. If you want to progress you MUST change.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9c0ba6fcb2c1c250b85e50c7d6bea6c8bdda47cf.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/change-is-good-all-the-time/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4cc7c070-8853-4e7b-ad57-ff89e6eab5e9</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:06:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EVERYTHING IS ART]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>EVERYTHING IS ART</h1><p>You are an artist… because everything is art. Loving others is “art” Good parenting is “art” Good teaching is “art” Learning is “art” Healthy living is “art” You get it….everything is “art.” My daughter has an art class one day a week at her school. She loves it. They do a great job helping her draw and paint scenarios she has experienced. Maybe it’s a trip we’ve made or her just playing with her cousins outside. But, then at home there are the times I’ll see her grab her crayons and a sheet of paper and just draw shapes, glue pieces of paper and add glitter. Then she’ll ask me, “Daddy is this art?” I always respond, “Everything is art.” Art is the expression or application of human creative skill and imagination. (apple dictionary) Do you see yourself as an artist? You should. You have lots of creative “one of a kind” bones in your body. You’re the only one of you. One of the most important parts of art is that it encourages a reaction. Most of us look to encourage a positive reaction. A reaction that attracts. A reaction that motivates. A reaction that supports our personal values. When my daughter asks me if what she created is art, what impresses me the most is that she doesn’t ask me if it is “good” art. She doesn’t have to ask. Based on my reaction, she knows it is something that brings a smile to my face, so she’ll try it again. When you see yourself as an artist you won’t rest on successes because you’ll never stop creating and you aren’t destroyed by your failures because all you did was get that one out of the way. Take the time to glean knowledge and experience from those who went before you, ask why, and learn. Then make art. You are making art whether you know it or not. So, if you’re going to sit down in front of a canvas, might as well make it an original. </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5eb33184-7fbc-4671-8176-d65839a1e06d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/everything-is-art/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">776933ec-e0e2-49a4-8e52-bcf807386d19</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:05:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[1+1+1 = 99]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>1+1+1 = 99</h1><p>Last night, on my way home from work, I called my wife and I could tell she was pretty stressed out. The kids had gotten on her last nerve. My son pooped his pants three times, he peed on the floor, and he and his sister wouldn’t stop bickering. 3 things throughout the day had brought some stress, but just 3? From the time we were little, we were taught that 1+1+1 = 3. But from the above example we see, with the right circumstances, 1+1+1 can equal WAY more than 3. It can feel like 1+1+1 = 99. So, when the right things get added in the right way at the right time, addition and subtraction rules get thrown out the window. Synergy – the interaction of elements that when combined produce a total effect that is greater than the sum of the individual elements, contributions, etc.; synergism. Most kids are masters of synergy. They can make you feel like there are several hundred of them, when in fact, there are just 2 or 3. But what about positive synergy? When, as a group, you can recognize and cultivate the different strengths that everyone individually can bring to the table, the result can be much more than just adding up the number of people. Don’t limit yourself to think that adding someone to your 5 person team will equal 6. It could equal much more than that, but it has to be the right person, in the right way, and at the right time. If you’re the one adding to a team, don’t demand synergy…provide the best opportunity for it. If you’re the team being added to, envision the opportunity each addition will bring. The exponential growth is up to you…whoever you are. </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8924f3b3-ac15-4be7-96ea-013e31cccf7d.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/111-99/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2f0f9c6c-a036-4981-8586-bc4b0a97dd8f</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:05:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I’ll poop on the potty on Friday. ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>I’ll poop on the potty on Friday. </h1><p>So, my wife and I are working on potty training our three year old little boy… He just won’t get excited about going poop on the toilet. When he poops in his diaper, I ask him when he is going to start pooping on the potty? Every time, he responds, “I’ll poop on the potty on Friday.” It doesn’t matter what day it is…he always tells me he’ll do it on Friday. I’m not sure why he picks Fridays and I’m not sure he even knows why he picks Fridays. What he does know, is that he will handle that later. He’ll put it on the schedule. He’ll give it a date and plan, so I’ll feel better about letting it wait. I’m sure you can guess what happens when Friday rolls around. You got it, he tells me he’ll do it next Friday. Again, he’ll schedule it and try to make me feel good that he is planning for it. Obviously, I know it can’t continue this way, but his example really made me think if I figuratively schedule myself to poop on Fridays? Do I consistently push things that need to get done? Do I schedule them, reschedule them, and then reschedule them without any real intent to get it done, until it becomes absolutely urgent? I recognized that my 3 year old and I had a lot in common. We, both in our own way, will poop on Fridays. My advice to him would be, “You’ll feel so good when you go on the potty. You’ll feel good that you did something you were scared to do yesterday. Most of all, you’ll feel so good and free that you don’t have to walk around everyday with poop in your pants.” Could I take my own advice? Absolutely! When I put off things until tomorrow or procrastinate I need to see myself as walking around with a “stinky load” in my pants. Don’t wait until Friday to get done what you need to. Realistically, schedule yourself. Set out to accomplish you’re plan. Know that your day will not go as planned, so plan for that. Don’t take short cuts like buying a great smelling air freshener to mask the “stinky load” you’re carrying around. Take advantage of the freedom and exuberance you’ll feel when you can release yourself of those tasks that have been binding you up…and don’t wait until Friday. This freedom can be and should be felt daily.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7017afe8-b42d-4259-b593-fe9a178c162e.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/ill-poop-on-the-potty-on-friday/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">529b1772-a925-449e-9129-14e08fdbff23</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>