<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Shuggeffect]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Shuggeffect]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:14:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ YOU BETTER HAVE A PURPOSE!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1> YOU BETTER HAVE A PURPOSE!</h1><p>What is your purpose? Steven Covey tells us in his book “The Seven Habits of Highly Effective People,” that we should “begin with the end in mind.” We should have a goal or a result in mind. So, if I were to ask you “what is the purpose of your company?”, could you answer with something other than, “to make a profit”? If I were to ask you, “what is the purpose of your position or department?”, could you answer with full confidence? It is very easy to get sucked-in to the latest trend or to follow the path that someone is telling you works for them, but what if your mission or purpose isn’t the same? How would you identify if the decision is a good or bad one? You could weigh it against why you are doing what you do. You could weigh it against your mission statement, but around here we call it the purpose. I read recently that Herb Kelleher, the founder of Southwest Airlines, said he wanted to be the most economical airline. He liked to have fun, but he was adamant that Southwest would not vary from the purpose of the company. Once, someone suggested they serve a nice chicken caesar salad on flights, and he responded with a question. He asked if that would help them to be the most economical airline? Of course the answer was no, so it was an easy decision to make. He had a purpose and his company made decisions based on that purpose. Even more importantly, his employees got behind that purpose and helped him keep it alive and thrive. They had a clear direction to follow and based all of their decisions on it. If you’re not sure about his leadership style, according to Wikipedia, “Fortune has also called him perhaps the best CEO in America.” </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/21c7574a2db889749ebf192d667a1fc8fac05f59.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/you-better-have-a-purpose/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d22b90d3-1709-4aff-82e9-fd378e0ae777</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:14:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A BULL NAMED FU MANCHU]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A BULL NAMED FU MANCHU</h1><p>Tim Nichols and Craig Wiseman wrote a song titled “Live Like You Were Dying” which was made famous by Country Music Star, Tim McGraw. The song is about a man that finds out he has cancer and starts living his life to the fullest. The first verse asks the question “How’s it hit ya, when you get that kind of news, man what’d ya do?” The chorus answers: I went sky divin’, I went rocky mountain climbin’, I went 2.7 seconds on a bull named Fu Manchu. And I loved deeper, And I spoke sweeter, And I gave forgiveness I’ve been denying, And he said someday I hope you get the chance, To live like you were dyin’. If I were dying, I would not go sky diving. I would love to climb a mountain though. And bull riding would be so cool!!! But competing in a Tractor Pull contest tops my list for sure! Would I love deeper? Would I speak sweeter? Would I give forgiveness that I have been denying? I want to believe so. My father passed away from pancreatic cancer in 1998 at the age of 68. He was an amazing man that lived a life of many interests. He loved the theater, collecting art and helping people in need financially. He was always very adamant that his name was never attached to a gift or donation. William John Lesperance was diagnosed in July and died one month later. Just before he passed, his words to me were “I should have gone fishing more.” I responded to him with “dad, you hated fishing.” He answered, “you just don’t get it son, because that is what I taught you. I worked my entire life. You need to learn to enjoy your life.” Interestingly enough, the next verse of the song is: And all the sudden goin’ fishing, Wasn’t such an imposition. And I went three times that year I lost my dad. Well I finally read the good book, And I took a good long hard look at what I’d do If I could do it all again. Reality Check! From the minute we are born, we start to die. So why would I need to face a desperate situation to start forgiving or loving more? As the song states, “The Good Book” – John recorded Jesus’s words in the 13th Chapter, “A new commandment I give unto you, That you love one another; as I have loved you, that you also love one another.” Reality Check #2! Christ commands it. He didn’t suggest it, He commands it! He didn’t say wait until . . . He said do it now. A close friend from Life Time Fitness has a quote that she uses in her emails. It reads, “Never doubt that a small group of thoughtful, committed citizens can change the world; indeed, it’s the only thing that ever has.” If I change, if I love, if I smile it will become contagious. Christ came and changed history with a small group of followers. He set the example, now it is up to me to follow. I want to start today. Change my pattern, smell the flowers and go fishing. Take on a challenge that interests you. Ride a Bull named Fu Manchu and Live Like You Were Dying!</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/134f9ce5dcaa127806ba3a60b07592a351f57e6f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/a-bull-named-fu-manchu/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0960fa3b-3d8f-405d-aae4-45d6df4a290a</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:14:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WHAT IS PERFECTION?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>WHAT IS PERFECTION?</h1><p>Is perfection always getting it right? Is it always being right? You might be saying, yes…of course, that is perfection, and you would be right. On the other hand, is learning a life long lesson from a mistake perfection? Is giving others more than they expect perfection? Is sharing excitement with those who are not excited perfection? I hope you are thinking that the above examples are perfection also. I’m not perfect and neither are you. The only perfection we can strive for is to react to imperfections perfectly. If I was only given what I deserved, then I would have never progressed. From the day I was born, I was given undeserved love, compassion, wisdom, and much more. If we only give or share with others what they deserve, we support the idea of imperfection. We spread imperfection because imperfection was shared with us. But, when we give more than necessary, when we love those who don’t love us, and we speak well of those who don’t deserve it, we react to those imperfections, that we all have, with perfection. We prove that perfection is possible and is actually generated by others imperfections. Perfection comes by imperfection? Absolutely! So the next time someone frustrates you, pulls one over on you, seems ungrateful, or is selfish…show them perfection by giving them more than they expect back. This is only way you and I can attain perfection. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/cc04d54d5f22c78e169530b2faddcdb916c170d4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/what-is-perfection/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d98a0823-1a42-41bb-ae55-4c21b980581f</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:14:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WATCH OR GET IN?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>WATCH OR GET IN?</h1><p>Recently I went to Great Wolf Lodge, an indoor hotel/waterpark with my little family. We had a blast…my kids did not want to leave. We spent a lot of time going down water slides and getting water dumped on us. While we were there, I noticed many parents just sending their children off to play on the slides and activities, as they remained comfortably seated at a table doing crossword puzzles or tinkering around on their phones or tablets. Their children would come and check in from time to time. The parents and children would laugh together about what fun the experience was. Then the children would bolt off, get back to having fun, and the moms or dads would get back to what they were engaged in. Understand, that I’m not looking to make judgements about those parents. What I would like to do is think about whether or not the experience could have been better, if mom and dad were sliding down the slides with their children rather than just providing the experience? I’m sure you’ll guess that my wife and I were racing our kids down the slides not just going down with them. It was awesome…during that time we found out which slides our kids liked the most. We helped them go down those slides more often and encouraged them to try new ones so they could try them all out. The kids loved seeing Gina and I get excited and pumped about going down the next slide. What made the experience in my eyes, was the interaction. The water slides were secondary. It made me think…Am I getting on the water slides with my customers? Do I really get to know what they enjoy and how to encourage them to try something new? Do I see our interaction as the most important thing rather than the service I provide? Of course, I would be doing my job by just providing what is asked for and then hanging tight until something else is needed. But wouldn’t the experience be better if I was right there understanding what is needed without waiting? If we get on the slide with our customers we can ultimately provide the best experience outside of what is required. Don’t just watch…get in.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/57fb6e73-9b6b-4263-af79-65b48debbe71.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/watch-or-get-in/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7580bb69-dfaa-4476-bc14-89ec2946e30f</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:14:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WHAT INSPIRES YOU?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>WHAT INSPIRES YOU?</h1><p>I have the best ideas when I’m mowing the lawn or even people watching with a warm cup of coffee in my hand. That’s why when I really want to get creative and get the juices flowing, I sit down at my desk, put my hands on the key board of my computer, and…NOTHING! That’s right…NOTHING! I just told you when I have my best ideas. Why would I expect new ideas and inspiration to come sitting at my desk staring at a computer screen. What inspires you? What activities give you new innovative ideas? What keeps you from getting wrapped up in the way you always do things? Whatever it is for you, spend more time doing it…and the scariest thing of all is, I think, you should do more of it AT WORK! A half hour of people watching and ten new ideas is way more valuable than 3 hours of thinking, surfing the web, checking Facebook, then thinking some more, checking Facebook, and one copied idea from Pinterest. If work is a place where progress should happen then spend time making progress. There are no rules about what work work looks like. But there are mathematical rules about work and this one is my favorite. Power = Work/Time If you want “POWER,” then you must do the most “WORK” in the shortest amount of “TIME.” This happens when you are inspired, passionate, and driven. Don’t spend SO much time doing what APPEARS to be work and do more of what inspires you to do REAL work. The best part of all, is that you won’t feel like you worked a day of your life. </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/498f6463-6af7-4730-b3ef-5b8376c086d2.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/what-inspires-you/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">00a96513-1e15-4c29-ace7-3011e82315c1</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:13:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ARE YOU A WINNER?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/85b7f8b0-9673-4e8e-a0d8-0f254a03cd7a.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/are-you-a-winner/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">085ad0fa-324c-44fa-9e3a-3c9137bc42e4</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:13:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[THE SECRET TO BEING #1 ON ANY GOOGLE SEARCH]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>THE SECRET TO BEING #1 ON ANY GOOGLE SEARCH</h1><p>Last week I was able to go to my first Daddy Daughter dance, and I had an absolute blast! It was a memory that I will always hold near and dear to my heart. When we arrived I was relieved of a fear that my little girl would be nervously attached to my leg. I was happy to see her dancing right in the middle of all the action. It was a mosh pit of little girls dancing to all their favorite songs. I was proud to see my little Ava had invested herself with enough of the girls that it carried over into the evening. Over the school year, she must have become invested with her friends through playing together, helping each other, and in some way giving and receiving value to each other. Then, when the big night came, it was organic (a natural occurrence) that she would be where the action was. I couldn’t have paid to have this happen if I wanted to. Ava and her friends could teach us a few things about making it up the Google ladder. Yes, a bunch of six-year-olds could teach us a thing or two. Maybe, just maybe, it isn’t about paying for someone to get your website to the top, or creating some hidden code that makes Google think you are more relevant and valuable than you really are. Maybe it is actually about being valuable? If you take the time to invest in your customers, allow them to provide honest feedback, provide them with valuable resources, and make it difficult for them not to talk positively about you with their friends, Google will have no choice but to bring you up the list. Regardless of their “new” algorithm. Sound like too much work? Sounds like it would take too long? If you’re looking for true, lasting friends/customers that will jump in the mosh pit with you, then there is no alternative. Bring value with what you do and you won’t have to rely on tactics and tricks. You’ll organically grow relationships that will last much longer than any paid click or search. Sometimes, it literally pays to think like a six- year-old.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f852b307c16a4739336228919a8819afb8436303.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/the-secret-to-being-1-on-any-google-search/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a0ef1f27-70f5-416f-9fa4-2de8aa0e3504</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:13:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Question?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Question?</h1><p>There is a question that is so simple it can be asked in one word. Most of the time, when  asked this question, we feel bothered to even try to answer it…but when WE ask it, we will search high and low for the answer. Many times, it is the most important question ever asked.

The question is…

Why?

Don’t ever be afraid to ask it and don’t be intimidated by being asked it.  The question,  “Why?” is important because it forces you, me, her, him, everyone to search and explore.

Why do we do it that way?

Why can’t we try something new?

Why is this happening?

Why isn’t that working?

Why do you feel that way?

Why do I feel this way?

The most amazing part about the question “Why?” is that the answer is not important.  When exploring the “why” of something don’t get too hung up on the answer, but see how far the successes and failures along the way bring you.  Embrace both, and maybe, just maybe, you’ll start asking yourself, “Why not?”

</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c11835fa-ab5b-4228-88b1-d52e68bd509f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/question/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6d6e1b2e-6d68-4b93-a17b-156aa43cabad</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:12:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MAKE YOUR DESIGN FIT LIKE A SUIT.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>MAKE YOUR DESIGN FIT LIKE A SUIT.</h1><p>We are surrounded every day by pleasing design. It is a part of us whether we think we enjoy it, notice it, and appreciate it or not. Billboards, magazines and commercials all try to appeal to the audience through targeted design. When shopping for clothing, we are essentially designing the way we look with color, texture, smell, and even frames. When purchasing a men’s suit, the arm length of the suit jacket should expose about ½ inch of the dress shirt sleeve, along with ½ inch of the shirt collar above the jacket collar. Why? Just to keep tailors in business? Not at all. The ½ inch of exposed shirt frames the jacket, just as a frame does with a work of art on the wall. This element is often over-looked because we are unaware or think that the extra $50-$100 in tailoring is not worth it. I guess if you’re not selling suits, and your suit sleeves are too long, it’s not the end of the world. You should know though, your suit will never look as appealing as the suit on the mannequin. So, let’s say you are trying to sell your services and you want to start marketing your business. The first option, for most, is to open MS Word or Publisher and start designing a logo. Then, find the cheapest website provider along with some free business cards. Remember, you’re trying to tell the world they should purchase from you because you’re different and BETTER than anyone else (if you’re not, don’t even bother). Imagine going to buy a suit and the gentleman helping you does not have his suit properly tailored. Maybe, you don’t know all the ins and outs of how a suit should fit, but you can definitely tell the suit on the salesman does not look like the one on the mannequin. Or…imagine, you have a contractor come to your house to give you an estimate and you inquire about his tidiness…if he’ll clean up after himself every day. You look at his vehicle and it looks like his whole office is in the truck and it hasn’t been washed in a year. No matter what the contractor tells you, there is a reluctance to believe he’ll clean up if he can’t take care of his own stuff. The “design” of a business tells more about it than any words. So, when we want to show the world who we are, it might be a good idea to get someone involved who knows the basic elements of design. There are a lot of freelance artists that are chomping at the bit to get some design work into their portfolio. Their work is very affordable. Many would be surprised at how affordable it is to get a logo/corporate identity produced. The look can be very clean and simple, but designed to be pleasing to look at. Just like it is worth the extra $50 to get that suit fitting just right, or the $10 car wash, we should put in that little extra and make design a top priority or else we are wasting our time.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/93e726b88ef6fec2c25892b7b2433ed4db0627e3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/make-your-design-fit-like-a-suit/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7df1676d-4be6-4e61-9059-c784cbcdf5db</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:12:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BORING? IT’S ALL YOUR FAULT!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>BORING? IT’S ALL YOUR FAULT!</h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/edef3ffe98cb6174183078593fd1efce218878b6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/shuggeffect/boring-its-all-your-fault/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c7e49144-96c2-4dc2-a8bd-33030a5d3ea9</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 18:12:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>